Guide to the Sarah P. Duke Gardens records, 1926-2012 UA.10.08.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Larry T. Daniel papers, 1934-2012, 2 boxes
  - Development Projects, 1960-2001
    - Meyer Bridge, 1991-1993 (Box 7)
    - Meyer Lewis Lantern, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Meyer Step Project, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Millstones, 1932-1991 (Box 7)
    - Moylan Bench Azalea Court, 1997 (Box 7)
    - NC Granite Cap, 1984-1987 (Box 7)
    - Nurses Bench, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
    - Olsby Millstone, 1993-1994 (Box 7)
    - Orchid Garden/Bone Marrow Transplant Project, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Paneck Bench, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Peduzzi Bench, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Pendly Bench, 1999-2000 (Box 7)
    - Pergada Plaque, 1939 April 17 (Box 7)
    - Pergola Flagstone, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Pinnell, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Pokorny Millstone, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Pond, Bog, and Pavillion Blomquist, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Pump House, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Retention Pond, 1982-1985 (Box 7)
    - Robinson Bench, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
    - Roberts Rocks Blomquist, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Rose Circle, 1963-1968 (Box 7)
    - Rose Garden, Leong Sketch, 1962 (Box 7)
    - Ross Family, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
    - Ross Gate, 1995-2001 (Box 7)
    - Rubridge, 1994-1996 (Box 7)
    - Runte Zig-Zag Bridge, 1993-1995 (Box 7)
    - Schiebel (Gate), 1991-1993 (Box 7)
    - Semans Fountain, 1988-1992 (Box 7)
    - Simes Rock, 1994-1996 (Box 7)
    - Sharp Azalea Ct. Bench, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Shelton Pond, 1991-1994 (Box 7)
    - Smith Lantern, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
    - Snow View Myer, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Starling Shelter, 1991-1993 (Box 7)
    - Street Plantings, Undated (Box 7)
    - Sundial Semans, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Terraces, 1961 (Box 7)
    - Terrace Garden Walkway, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Tweed Memorial, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Vaughn Bench, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Vaughn, Mary Rock Set, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
    - Walker Bench, 1988-1995 (Box 7)
    - Walkway, 1981-1987 (Box 7)
    - Wherrett Bench, 1999-2000 (Box 7)
    - Willard, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
    - 36th Parallel Marker, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - General Files, 1934-2002
    - ASLA Award, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Biddle-Semans, 1975-1991 (Box 8)
    - Blomquist, H.L, 1965-1977 (Box 8)
    - Boundaries, 1959-1979 (Box 8)
    - Building Inspections, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Direction for Gardens, 1934-2002 (Box 8)
    - Ed Steffek Memorial Service, 1991-2001 (Box 8)
    - Elizabeth Hanes Corresponence, 1950-1960 (Box 8)
    - Ellen Shipman, 1977-1997 (Box 8)
    - Fillmore Letters and Notes, 1952-1967 (Box 8)
    - Fillmore, R.H., 1977-1978 (Box 8)
    - Howard, Initialize Master Plan, 1959-1961 (Box 8)
    - Hurricane Fran, 1996-1997 (Box 8)
    - IMS Grant Application, 1995-1996 (Box 8)
    - Jewell, 1986-1987 (Box 8)
    - Ledger, 1946-1959 (Box 8)
    - Leong, Larry, 1958-1974 (Box 8)
    - Leong, William, 1969-1978 (Box 8)
    - Leong, Obit. Rememberances, 1986-1988 (Box 8)
    - Mary Duke Biddle, 1960-1980 (Box 8)
    - Photographs, 1952-1995 (Box 8)
    - Report, 1934-1938 (Box 8)
    - Shipman Symposium, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Soil Types, 1960s (Box 8)
    - Webb, 1937-1938 (Box 8)
    - Wister Correspondence, 1934-1936 (Box 8)
    - 40th, 50th Anniversery, 1979-1989 (Box 8)
  - Orders, 1945-2001
    - Early Orders, Fillmore, 1962-1969 (Box 8)
    - Old Invoices, 1945-1966 (Box 8)
    - Orders, 1964-1989 (Box 8)
    - Plant Orders, 1967-2001 (Box 8)
    - 90s Orders, 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Plants, 1935-2001
    - Cephalotaxus, 1976-1980 (Box 8)
    - Cephalotaxus, 1994-1997 (Box 8)
    - Dawn Redwood, 1973-1998 (Box 8)
    - Metasequoia, 2000-2001 (Box 8)
    - Narcissus, 1935-1940 (Box 8)
    - Redwoods, 1997-2000 (Box 8)
  - Publicity and Publications, 1936-2012
    - American Horticulturlist, "Going South", 1976 (Box 8)
    - Arnoldia, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Flora, 1967-2001 (Box 8)
    - Garden Correspondence and Publicity, 1945-1958 (Box 8)
    - Garden History, Publicity, 1956-2001 (Box 8)
    - The Garden Journal, 1964 (Box 8)
    - The Garden Journal, Reprints, 1964 (Box 8)
    - Horticultural Magazine, Guide to the City Trees in the Boston Area, 1952-1976 (Box 8)
    - Landscape Architecture (Leong), 1959 (Box 8)
    - Old Newspaper Articles, 1972-2001 (Box 8)
    - Old Newspaper Articles, 1952-1989 (Box 8)
    - Old Newspaper Articles, 1964-1988 (Box 8)
    - Other Gardens, Undated (Box 8)
    - Other Gardens, Undated (Box 8)
    - Southern Accents, 1978-1987 (Box 8)
    - Annual Reports, 2001-2004 (Box 9)
    - Annual Reports, 2005-2008 (Box 9)
    - Annual Reports, 2009-2012 (Box 9)
    - Calendars, 2007-2009 (Box 9)
    - Calendars, 2010-2013 (Box 9)
    - Chronicle Gardens Issue, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Development Plan, Board of Advisors Minutes, 1936-1997 (Box 9)
    - Education Committee Report, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Guide to Duke Gardens, Undated (Box 9)
    - Historical Materials, 1935-1999 (Box 9)
    - Photographs, 2009 (Box 9)
    - Photographs, 1944-2009 (Box 9)
    - Promotional Artifact, 2009 (Box 9)
    - Publicity, Letters, 1938-2001 (Box 10)
    - Lecture and Educational Series, 1996-2003 (Box 10)
    - Clippings and Photographs, 1993-1996 (Box 10)
    - Publicity, 1994-1995 (Box 10)
    - Publicity, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Brochures, Undated (Box 10)
    - Education and Events Guide, 1995-2013 (Box 10)
    - Ornament (artifact), Undated (Box 11)
    - Duke Gardens (CD), Undated (Box 11)
    - "Crown Jewel of Duke University" (DVD), 2004 (Box 11)
    - Panoramic Photographs, 1993 and Undated (Box 11)
- Garden Drawings and Designs, 1935-1999, Located on-site in oversize storage
  - John C. Wister Drawings and Designs, 1935-1936
    - Planting and Plot Plan, 1 sheet, diazo (2 copies), 1935 Dec. (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Planting plan near the house of Dr. F. M. Hanes, 1 sheet, diazo, 1936 Jan. (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Planting and plot plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1935 Dec. (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Ellen Shipman Drawings and Designs, 1937-1939
    - Pool and Garden House, sections and details drawings, 1 sheet, blueprint, 1937 June (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Construction drawing for Central Pool, 1 sheet, blueprint, 1937 June (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Construction drawing for Pool A, 1 sheet, blueprint, 1937 June (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Construction drawing for Pool B, 1 sheet, blueprint, 1937 Aug. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Planting plan for planting on bank, 1 sheet, blueprint, 1937 Sept. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Proposed office building, working drawing, 1 sheet, blueprint, 1937 Oct. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Plan for naturalistic planting between garden and bank and woods, planting plan, 1 sheet, blueprint with colored pencil, 1937 Nov. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Proposed pergola for Duke Univ., working drawing drawn by J.S., 1 sheet, blueprint, 1937 Nov. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Proposed pergola for Duke Univ., half plan of stairs, drawn by J.S., 1 sheet, blueprint, 1937 Nov. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Proposed pergola for Duke Univ., working drawing drawn by J.S., 1 sheet, blueprint, revised 1937 Dec. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - zproposed pergola for Duke Univ., half plan of stairs, drawn by J.S., 1 sheet blueprint, revised 1937 Dec. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Proposed pergola for Duke Univ., finial and newel post details, drawn by J.S., 1 sheet, blueprint, 1937 Dec. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Planting plan for wild slope above pond, working drawing, 1 sheet, blueprint on linen, 1938 Jan. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Plan to show location of rock ledges above pond, working drawing, 1 sheet, blueprint on linen, 1938 Jan. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Planting plant for shrubs on bank behind garden house, working drawing, 1 sheet, blueprint, 1938 April (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Planting plan for the bank south of the Sarah P. Duke Memorial Garden, working drawing, 1 sheet, blueprint, 1939 June (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Finial detail drawing, 1 sheet, blueprint, undated (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Plan showing location of garden, topographical map, 1 sheet, blueprint, undated (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Plans of walks, section B working drawing, 1 sheet, blueprint, undated (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Plan of walks, section A, 1 sheet, ink on linen, undated (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Plan of walks, section B, 1 sheet, ink on linen, undated (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Planting plan for the area around the pool, working drawing, 1 sheet, blueprint, undated (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Proposed pergola for Duke Univ., section plans, 1 sheet, blueprint, undated (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Section 1-L on center line, elevation drawing, 1 sheet, blueprint, undated (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Topographical map, section of Sarah P. Duke Gardens, 1 sheet, blueprint, undated (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Proposed office building, working drawing, 1 sheet, electrostatic copy, 1937 Oct. (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Planting plan for trees and shrubs, section A, 1 sheet, electrostatic on paper, 1938 March (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Planting plan for trees and shrubs, section B, 1 sheet, electrostatic on paper, 1938 March (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Perennial planting plan, section B, 1 sheet, electrostatic copy on paper, 1938 April (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Perennial planting plan, section C, 1 sheet, electrostatic copy on paper, 1938 April (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Perennial planting plan, section D, 1 sheet, electrostatic copy on paper, 1938 April (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Perennial planting plan, section A, 1 sheet, electrostatic copy on paper, undated (Oversize-folder 2)
  - William S. Leong Drawings and Designs, also drawings based on his designs, 1958-1977
    - Area treatment around office and tool house, sketch, 1 sheet, diazo., 1958 Aug. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Area treatment around office, sketch, 1 sheet, diazo., 1958 Aug. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Hanes Memorial Garden and vicinity, landscape design drawing, 1 sheet, diazo w/pencil, 1958 Sept. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Anderson Street entrance, working drawing, modified from Leong by R.H. Fillmore, 1 sheet, pencil on tracing paper. 1958 Feb.; revised 1958 Oct. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Hanes entrance, drawn by R.H. Fillmore after William S. Leong design, 1 sheet, diazo, 1958 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Memorial area approach, site plan, by H.J. Copeland based on Leong master plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1959 May (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Master Plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1959 May (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Anderson Street entrance general plan, site plan, R. H. Fillmore adapted from William S. Leong, 1 sheet, diazo, 1959 Oct. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Anderson Street entrance clearing plan, working drawing, by R.H. Fillmore adapted from William S. Leong, 1 sheet, diazo, 1959 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Service building, rough drawing by R.H. Fillmore based on William S. Leong plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1960 Dec. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Anderson Street entrance, preliminary design, 1 sheet, diazo, 1961 March (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Anderson gates and post design, design development drawings, 1 sheet, diazo, 1961 Dec. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Anderson gate entrance, elevation drawing by R. H. Fillmore, after William S. Leong, 1 sheet, pencil on tracing paper, 1961 Dec. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Anderson Street entrance, presentation drawing, 1 sheet, colored pencil on paper, 1961 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Terrace-Pavilion fountain area, working drawings, 4 sheets, diazo, 1963 Sept. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Spray pond fountain plan, electrical, utility and mechnaical plans, 3 sheets, pencil on vellum, 1963 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Terrace-Pavilion and fountain pool, structural plan, 4 sheets, pencil on vellum, 1963 Sept. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Blomquist Area, sketches, 1 sheet, pencil on vellum, 1964 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Master plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1959, revised 1964 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Trellis design, plan and elevation drawing, William S. Leong, 1 sheet, diazo, 1965 Jan. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Main entrance, site plan, taken from Leong master plan, drawn by LTD, 1 sheet, diazo, 1969 June (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Storm drainage, preliminary study, 1 sheet, diazo, 1975 Aug. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Master plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1977 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Master plan, 1 sheet, sepia on vellum, 1959 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Master plan, 1 sheet, diazo w/numerous pencil notes and calculations, 1959; revised 1967 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Spray pond, site plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1961 July (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Azalea court area, preliminary plot plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1961 Aug. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Azalea court area, preliminary plot plan with some planting notations, 1 sheet, diazo with colored pencil, 1961 Aug. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Spray pond, copy of Leong tracing with vegetion notes by R.H. Fillmore, 1 sheet, diazo w/pencil, 1963 Jan. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Fountain and vicinity, schematic planting plan, ultimate construction, 1 sheet, diazo, 1963 March (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Fountain and vicinity, layout and grading plan, first construction, 1 sheet, diazo, 1963 March (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Fountain and vicinity, layout and grading plan, ultimate construction, 1 sheet, diazo, 1963 March (Oversize-folder 3)
    - South half of Duke Gardens gate showing post for new panel, 1 sheet, diazo, 1972 May (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Master plan, unmarked, 1 sheet, mylar, 1977 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Master Plan with corrections by Larry T. Daniel, 1 sheet, diazo with pencil, 1977 June 15; corrections 1977 June 17 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Elevation drawing of steps, after William S. Leong, 1 sheet, pencil on graph vellum, undated (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Terrace-Pavilion fountain area, section drawing along Sta.4+00, 1 sheet, pencil on graph vellum, undated (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Azalea court area, schematic Plans A-F, 6 sheets, pencil on vellum, undated (Oversize-folder 3)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Vine Arbor, elevation and plan drawing per R.H. Fillmore, 1 sheet, pencil on vellum, 1965 Jan. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Garden trellis, design drawing, 2 sheets, pencil on vellum, 1967 Nov. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Garden trellis, design drawing, reduced size, 1 sheet, pencil on tracing paper, 1971 May (Oversize-folder 3)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Vine arbor, working drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, 1976 Dec. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Master plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1976 Dec. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Master plan, 1 sheet, diazo with pencil notations and revisions, 1976 Dec. (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Linda Jewell Drawings and Designs, 1979-1995
    - Retention pond landscape plan, presentation drawing, 1 sheet, diazo with colored marker, 1982 Dec. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Entry plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1991 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Azalea court, plan and elevation drawings, Hayter Reynolds and Jewell, 2 sheets, diazo, 1992 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Retention pond dam, working drawings, 6 sheets, diazo, 1992 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Bird watching pavillion, working drawings, 3 sheets, diazo, 1998 June (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Flood control scheme B-permanent pond, site plan, 1 sheet, diazo and colored marker, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Handicap ramp, topographical map, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Truckworthy bridge and garden plan, conceptual drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Pool gazing arbor, progress plan and elevation drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, 1991 March (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Pool gazing arbor, working drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, 1991 May; revised 1991 June (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Pedestrian bridge, design development drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, 1991 June (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Entrance gate, working drawings, 2 sheets, diazo, 1991 Aug. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Pathways, site plan, 1991 Aug. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Pedestrian bridge, working drawings, 3 sheets, diazo, note: marked "Not for Construction," 1991 Sept. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Entrance gate, site plan and elevation drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, 1991 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Master plan, development drawing, 1 sheet, diazo with ink and colored pencil, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Master plan, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: General site plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1984 June (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Garden pond, presentation drawing, 1 sheet, colored pencil on mat board, 1991 May (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Garden pond, site plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1991 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Garden gate, design drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, 1993 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Garden gate, structural detail drawings, 6 sheets, diazo, 1995 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Garden gate weather vane, size criteria plan, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: General site plan and shelter elevation drawings, 3 sheets, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L. Blomquist Garden: Shelton pond, working drawings, 3 sheets, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Design development drawing (first draft), 1 sheet, diazo, circa 1985 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Pool gazing arbor, working drawing (marked Construction drawing), 1 sheet, diazo with colored marker, 1991 May (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Bridge and iris garden, presentation drawing, 1 sheet, diazo and colored pencil, 1991 June (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Pedestrian bridge, working drawings, 3 sheets, diazo, 1991 Aug. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Entrance gate, working drawings, 2 sheets, diazo, 1991 Oct. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arboretum: Pond and shelter, presentation drawing, 2 sheets, diazo, 1993 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arborteum: Eitokuji lantern, elevation and site plan drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, 1993 July (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arborteum: Eitokuji lantern, design development drawing Option A, 1 sheet, diazo, 1993 July (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arborteum: Eitokuji lantern, design development drawing Option B, 1 sheet, diazo, 1993 July (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arborteum: Arched footbridge, design development drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, 1995 Sept. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arborteum: Arched footbridge, plan and detail drawings, 1 sheet, diazo, 1995 Oct. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arborteum: Entrance gate, concept drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Asiatic Arborteum: North end-proposed Asiatic Garden, site plan, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L Blomquist Garden: Garden structure, working drawings, 7 sheets, diazo, 1984 Dec. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L Blomquist Garden: Shelter, plan and elevation drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, circa 1984 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L Blomquist Garden: Millstones, location plan, 1 sheet, diazo with pencil, 1991 Sept. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L Blomquist Garden: Information kiosk, elevation drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, 1995 June (Oversize-folder 4)
    - H.L Blomquist Garden: Gohdes Blomquist Garden grape arbor, working drawings, 3 sheets, ink jet, 1999 Feb. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Revised master plan, 1 sheet, diazo with colored marker, 1979 Oct. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Entry, plan and elevation drawing of information bollards, 1 sheet, diazo, 1991 July (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Handicap access, site plan and elevation, 1 sheet, diazo, 1991 May; revised 1991 Aug. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Rose garden fountain, conceptual drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, 1991 Sept. (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Entrance information area, working drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, 1992 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Bridge finial, detail drawings, full scale, 1 sheet, pencil and colored pencil on paper, 1993 (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Bridge finial, detail drawing, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Master plan, exisiting conditions, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Rose garden pool, schematic drawings, 2 sheets, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Schematic drawing, 1 sheet, electrostatic copy, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
    - Rose court, design drawings, 2 sheets, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 4)
  - Doris Duke Center - Atkin, Olshin, Lawson-Bell & Associates Architects, Nelson-Boyd Landscape Architects, 1996-1999
    - Center for Duke Gardens, preliminary design drawings, 6 sheets, diazo, 1996 Oct. (Oversize-folder 5)
    - Doris Duke Center for the Sarah P. Duke Memorial Gardens, design development drawings, 5 sheets, diazo, 1999 (Oversize-folder 5)
  - Maps, 1937-1991, undated
    - Topographical map of Sarah P. Duke Memorial Gardens, 1 sheet, diazo with pencil notations, 1937 Aug. (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Topographical map of Sarah P. Duke Memorial Gardens, 1 sheet, diazo, 1937 Aug.; Nov. (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Contour topography map, George Love, engineer, 1 sheet, blueprint, 1937 Nov. (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Campus map with parking lot locations and proposals, 1 sheet, diazo, 1950 (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Topographical map of Sarah P. Duke Memorial Gardens, by K.J. Tharp, 1 sheet, diazo, 1957 June (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Campus layout showing existing and proposed drives and parking, drawn by Al Norton, engineer, W.K. Howard, 1 sheet, diazo, 1957 (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Hanes Memorial Garden, topographical plan, K.J. Tharp, engineer, drawn by K.R. Keene. This copy the working drawing of R.H. Fillmore, 1958 (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Topographical map of spray pond area, 1 sheet, diazo, 1961 June (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Illustrated Map, 1 sheet, electrostatic copy, undated (Oversize-folder 6)
    - City of Durham, aerial and topographical with buildings noted, sheet 6E, 1 sheet, diazo, 1951 March (Oversize-folder 6)
    - City of Durham, aerial and topographical with buildings noted, sheet 6F, 1 sheet, diazo, 1951 March (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Topographical map (Tharp), 1 sheet, diazo, with supplemental notes on Haines and Anderson St. entrance, 1957; Notes added 1959 (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Tharp topographical map with supplementary data on water system, 1 sheet, diazo with pencil, 1960 Jan. (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Tharp topographical map with supplementary data from W.H. Gardner Assoc., 1 sheet, diazo, 1961 Dec. (Oversize-folder 6)
    - West Campus sanitary sewer plan, 1 sheet, diazo, 1967 May (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Duke University Medical Center, 1 sheet, diazo, 1971 Oct. (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Become a Friend of Duke Gardens master plan map, 1 sheet, diazo with colored marker, 2nd ed., revised, 1991 (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Become a Friend of Duke Gardens master plan map, 1 sheet, electrostatic on paper, 2nd ed., revised, 1991 (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Master plan grid map, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Master plan map, 1 sheet, diazo with numerous pencil notes, undated (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Master plan grid map, 1 sheet, electrostatic on film, undated (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Topographical map of Durham showing Duke's West Campus and Athletic Fields, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Plot plan of West Campus, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Building locations map (supercedes plan drawn 1939 April 18), 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 6)
    - West Campus aerial survey and topographicap map, 1 sheet, diazo, undated (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Topographical map of Anderson Street entrance area, 1 sheet, diazo, 1965 Sept. (Oversize-folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1934-1993
    - Iris garden, plot plan, George F. Hackney, 1 sheet, diazo and colored pencil, 1934-1935 (Oversize-folder 7)